{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"d492d23e-5102-459d-91ef-4a72fee3cd41"},"exam":{"id":"7e4c72ad-e12b-4965-be9c-2cbc2c7ac079","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false}]},{"id":"8af9065f-42ab-4684-937d-6ff9a21fce3a","domain":"tech","question":"You visit a clients site and get called into a corridor discussion. You are asked to describe the new (2019) URL structure for objects in S3.  Which of these do you use as a description.","explanation":"AWS has updated the URL format for objects in S3 in order to partition the name space.  This will introduce more consistency, but be aware that there are still multiple variation depending on feature and location.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-path-deprecation-plan-the-rest-of-the-story/","title":"New S3 path format"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/rande.html#s3_region","title":"S3 Regional Endpoints"}],"answers":[{"id":"e9fd54ece61badbfe41eb84932fcb635","text":" http, then the object name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"9b571c57c4bcb1635a0422505e741908","text":" https, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":true},{"id":"db8e7027e46c062db1befedc330f0884","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"ae3cbeae173c8a519b7847f15141def6","text":" https, then the bucket name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"ab8096a72368e95dc6011f1758564494","text":" https, then the object name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"a91ee87d632a84e3d44d1f44d80dc38e","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"f2a5230ac12d8264aebebe8dfedd74a5","text":" http, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false}]},{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"a0b65082-209c-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"By default, how many buckets per AWS Account can you create with the Amazon S3 service?","explanation":"By default, you can create up to 100 S3 buckets per AWS account. However, you can request for additional buckets by submitting a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":false},{"id":"8e296a067a37563370ded05f5a3bf3ec","text":"25","correct":false},{"id":"f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd","text":"100","correct":true},{"id":"cee631121c2ec9232f3a2f028ad5c89b","text":"500","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false},{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false}]},{"id":"cd40e670-2ffc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Elastic Beanstalk?","explanation":"With Elastic Beanstalk, you can quickly deploy and manage web applications in the AWS Cloud without having to learn about the infrastructure that runs them. That’s what makes it a Platform as a Service. There is no charge for using Elastic Beanstalk itself; you are only charged for the underlying AWS resources that the application uses.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/latest/dg/Welcome.html","title":"What is AWS Elastic Beanstalk?"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"6efc4ed7a174b46c2ecebb016e0329eb","text":"It is Platform as a Service (PaaS).","correct":true},{"id":"2d4a6743e5521dc61e99fdb14ee7f4b1","text":"It is Software as a Service (SaaS).","correct":false},{"id":"0e2daa2a54c9f6d95ceebc8b65589f62","text":"It enables you to quickly deploy and manage web applications in the cloud.","correct":true},{"id":"20fb5a0ca00f262eed3b067bb1718e82","text":"There is a charge for using Elastic Beanstalk.","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false}]},{"id":"6ffbb1ad-0c02-4ae3-82ba-fa79a62e733b","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support pricing plans provide access to both the AWS Personal Health Dashboard and the AWS Health API?","explanation":"Having an AWS account grants you access to the Personal Health Dashboard to receive alerts and remediation guidance regarding events affecting the services underlying your resources. However, if you go with either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you will also get AWS Health API for integrating health data and notifications with your existing in-house and third-party IT management tools.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/health/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"What is AWS Health?"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"d4c61d1c-2ada-4bc2-9cf9-2546f8d62025","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid S3 bucket names?","explanation":"The 'January-2020-sales-numbers' is the only S3 bucket name that is not valid; bucket names must not contain uppercase letters, and they must start with a lowercase letter or number. The other three responses are valid, since they do not violate bucket naming rules.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"9b55e7cfabcca3d69f5596c5122f46b2","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/january-2020-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"799de5bb8d3ce8dd91b7c8416efaa490","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/January-2020-sales-numbers","correct":false},{"id":"5843ebf1fe3709048eb1d4ca8bdc00aa","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/012020-sales-numbers","correct":true},{"id":"429e0b5ab4b0f9b9f14d8be62cecde68","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2020-january-sales-numbers","correct":true}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false}]},{"id":"exqs7qpq-98m8-yh3n-9wpt-cj92guokdim7","domain":"tech","question":"When running a relational database on an EC2 instance, which of the following are you responsible for?","explanation":"When running a relational database on either your hardware or on an EC2 instance, you are responsible for all of these tasks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"cabb2d7f34e79fde9a777d14a747c49f","text":"Operating system maintenance","correct":false},{"id":"4c5d94eb4dc4bff93f6a96a08ab7b244","text":"Data security","correct":false},{"id":"48169bb807ca235b3d5db39768de325e","text":"Database backups and high-availability","correct":false},{"id":"1b924bbbc14b974d21d136baae3e2618","text":"None of these","correct":false},{"id":"7b4eef372e52b848a7e0f93e59b06d70","text":"All of these","correct":true},{"id":"00bef37d7138807bbf32a7e7fa1b3f95","text":"Software install and patches","correct":false}]},{"id":"su6exaen-uvfq-awbs-r1m3-y06rtjhsbaw6","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment. AWS Inspector can help you assess your security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"7e71f634-1fe3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Redshift?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift is AWS’s data warehouse service designed to scale up to petabytes of structured data. Using Redshift, you can create a data warehouse with a set of nodes, which is referred to as a 'cluster'.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c195feba1b6755cf70b23e85f649bea5","text":"It stores unstructured data.","correct":false},{"id":"1be4b9169c53e2842d313aa2e9fe2bc5","text":"It is a data warehouse service.","correct":true},{"id":"eae61ac52e73cabeaa3d471e1f2214dd","text":"It is designed for storing petabytes of data.","correct":true},{"id":"cb8783f4a61d2d6ce45ab561107c68fe","text":"It is used to launch a set of nodes called a Redshift cluster.","correct":true}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true}]},{"id":"024e0354-7a25-4a81-b42e-ce2af844e0e5","domain":"security","question":"Which service might you use to provide Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection to your applications running on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true}]},{"id":"1s9oou1o-9lmx-321m-4ite-iqy9x7zuv18y","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed database service that is compatible with MySQL, but provides better performance?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed database service that is up to 5X faster than a traditional MySQL database. PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, and MariaDB are all different database technologies which are not directly compatible with MySQL","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"399bd1ee587245ecac6f39beaa99886f","text":"PostgreSQL","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true}]},{"id":"jpt9cxq0-nxn2-jxb3-g66u-ucfgv69ofwnu","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are key components of Amazon Glacier?","explanation":"Data is organised in S3 into Archives, and Vaults are used to group Archives together. Access policies control who can access the data in Archives & Vaults. Buckets are a part of S3, but not Glacier. Volumes are often associated with hard disks and therefore EBS, while Tables are database constructs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"}],"answers":[{"id":"5b70a213f150f01f0776fa9481ef2ddf","text":"Vault","correct":true},{"id":"30edf70db68aa84f05d3e72326807b0c","text":"Bucket","correct":false},{"id":"bd7a9717d29c5ddcab1bc175eda1e298","text":"Volume","correct":false},{"id":"51c45b795d5d18a3e4e0c37e8b20a141","text":"Table","correct":false},{"id":"e727b00944f81e1d0a95c12886ac4641","text":"Archive","correct":true},{"id":"8e2ddf5878aac8b5d22a6acab856040d","text":"Access Policy","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"0b2dkrmk-derf-tm5u-h127-w4yffwtldij2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are Support Levels offered by AWS?","explanation":"AWS Support has four levels. Basic is their free entitlement for all AWS Customers. The three paid support plans in order of ascending cost are Developer, Business, and Enterprise. Start-up and Individual do not exist as Support Plans","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"3263b7364a2b2cb3d4697003ef512748","text":"Start-up","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":true}]},{"id":"77471ce7-4336-4912-9c33-ecfc5d174a41","domain":"billing","question":"You want to monitor your costs of using your AWS services and receive alerts when the thresholds you defined are met. Which of the following AWS Budget types should you create?","explanation":"You need to create a cost budget with AWS Budgets if you want to monitor the cost of using your AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/budgets-managing-costs.html","title":"Managing Your Costs with Budgets"}],"answers":[{"id":"7d45335a770dd2fc66658fb908bb7f9a","text":"Cost Budget","correct":true},{"id":"825a98fa534bb772e00d7b7571f0217f","text":"Reservation Budget","correct":false},{"id":"bd4ad96569591af6420d456b8176c90d","text":"Savings Plans Budget","correct":false},{"id":"3f3eb4d8c9ecc531c5a784bcc5e608b5","text":"Usage Budget","correct":false}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the company’s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false}]},{"id":"90df786a-99f7-45c0-b4ed-126bfc6c55de","domain":"concepts","question":"A mobile shopping list app needs to be able to add, delete, and update items on specific lists anytime a user desires. The backend for the app will run on Amazon EC2 instances with Auto Scaling to manage fluctuations in user demand. Many times, a user will perform maintenance on many list items in a single session. What design characteristic must be incorporated into the app for these requirements to be met?","explanation":"In order for horizontal scaling to be effective, you'll want to make sure the app doesn't store previous transaction or session information on specific EC2 instances. That way, any EC2 instance provisioned by Auto Scaling can process the request. Leveraging load balancing is also a good practice, but doesn't address the need for a stateless app. Session affinity goes the other direction, directing a load balancer to route transactions to a specific instance each time. Bootstrapping runs scripts each time an EC2 instance is provisioned.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud - AWS Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f3d1559e229505103abfd9297d2249c","text":"Make sure the app doesn’t need knowledge of previous transactions","correct":true},{"id":"175dc87c438249634b2c6104864a2e6a","text":"Leverage load balancing to distribute transactions to multiple nodes","correct":false},{"id":"712738cb3dbc4b4aeb218af7b44b731c","text":"Use bootstrapping on the EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"3169165ef00c3474aa673628039e0dc1","text":"Implement session affinity","correct":false}]},{"id":"cpv9q14j-4nnf-wb3n-urul-qo85pzcs4lot","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following best describes a Resource Group?","explanation":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsconsolehelpdocs/latest/gsg/what-are-resource-groups.html","title":"What Are Resource Groups?"}],"answers":[{"id":"02853c1436655d9187bb9d61a5b2ce70","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that share one or more tags or portions of tags.","correct":false},{"id":"dabdc344de93e3ccb3d5245b1f871f94","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"85a53afa2201152c277b7a584e2933be","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"7ff9ffa66bb042afad45110ef6296a1a","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","correct":true}]},{"id":"922bcb30-a895-4a3f-bb49-94c90e34a5ed","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services can Amazon CloudWatch use as a target to deliver near real-time streams of system events that describe changes in AWS resources?","explanation":"EC2 instances, AWS Lambda functions, and Amazon SQS queues are a few of the AWS services that can be configured as targets for CloudWatch events.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/events/WhatIsCloudWatchEvents.html","title":"What Is Amazon Cloudwatch Events?"}],"answers":[{"id":"f4fb4c65fcc06f70081c87f3a00cb3a3","text":"Redshift clusters","correct":false},{"id":"4fc99f94726d4b95eaa8250076dc8f6f","text":"AWS Lambda functions","correct":true},{"id":"e5c6ffd5e16261a07c150339d8a42610","text":"Amazon SQS queues","correct":true},{"id":"afe6e803ff73335b743f02267c6a3f17","text":"EC2 instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"f81195c4-7959-4925-a41d-e50f901cccad","domain":"tech","question":"Your System Administration team lead wants you to subscribe to the RSS feed to be notified of any interruptions to the EC2 service in the N. California and Ohio Regions. Which of the following will enable you to do that?","explanation":"Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, such as EC2, and it enables RSS subscription. The Personal Health Dashboard does provide information about the services you're using, but it does not give you the ability to subscribe to RSS feeds.","links":[{"url":"https://status.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Service Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"5b60dd28958c0d6d59a455cc074e4322","text":"Service Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"cf4db9f312542c8284a6ccdefcd98544","text":"Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"8e75b153e61c22a8ea4e14aadc7cb4ee","text":"Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"087edf830b5f3b392ebaef37ba8550f7","text":"EC2 Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"d3392ac3-0a35-4d09-a5e1-cdde62d620d8","domain":"tech","question":"You wish to set up a website consisting of 5 pages advertising your writing and editing services. The WordPress theme you have chosen for the site is a simple, straightforward text-and-image layout. Using the EC2 service to set up your WordPress website, which of the following would be the most cost-effective EC2 instance type to go with?","explanation":"A general purpose EC2 instance is the ideal choice, since it provides equal proportions of compute, memory, and networking resources. This website does not indicate that it needs a greater-than-usual proportion of memory, storage, or computing power.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"e65781ecdb4e2c3e7af2864d7b875e57","text":"Accelerated computing","correct":false},{"id":"4e8e31d149d66214d0c06fd9ee8b877b","text":"Compute optimized","correct":false},{"id":"3da02f3f7a678b5e2c167fb35dcea8f5","text":"General purpose","correct":true},{"id":"b4820282379b9534539d339e1d898f2b","text":"Storage optimized","correct":false},{"id":"a97bdc2a34beb1500a16c5a5f41d3234","text":"Memory optimized","correct":false}]},{"id":"4uvrqex2-fb79-fccq-6ogx-umyvygaxn7fi","domain":"security","question":"You are using your corporate directory to grant your users access to AWS services. What is this called?","explanation":"Federated Access is when you use an external directory, such as your coroporate one, to grant users in that directory access to AWS resources. Role-based and User group are more used to definied which resources a user is able to access once they have access, not the method by which they gain that access. Multifactor Authentication Access is the concept of a user requiring 2 secrets to be able to access the resources - usually their password and a 1 time code provided by a device under their control (e.g. a mobile phone).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/identity/federation/","title":"Identity Federation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d3973accf5dd88240811572d5f2608eb","text":"Multifactor Authentication Access","correct":false},{"id":"acce53b09f08060687cd88c30bce9db8","text":"Role-based Access","correct":false},{"id":"00347e1d2de42be9910e334d04fe60dc","text":"Federated Access","correct":true},{"id":"0db642c28b60c6a51547c3da2262902b","text":"User Group Access","correct":false}]},{"id":"4885465a-c1a0-41e2-8e7d-d6ac27557522","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following comprises an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?","explanation":"An AMI includes three types of information. There’s the Amazon EBS snapshot or snapshots for backing up EBS volume data to S3, or a template for the root volume of the instance if the AMI is instance-store-backed. There are launch permissions for controlling which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch an instance. And there’s block device mapping for specifying the volumes to attach to the instance when it’s launched. These are the pieces of information that AMI requires to launch an EC2 instance; the EC2 instance is part of the AMI itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/AMIs.html","title":"Amazon Machine Images (AMI) – Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f8a7b69b94bd2a5b6d397b35bf7a403","text":"EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"11d5f5efdfcf29972a22321321560da7","text":"EBS snapshots or root volume template of an EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"1dd2a814eff8bee8cf3e4da0ee6a245e","text":"Block device mapping","correct":true},{"id":"fb7756bd7b1e9872836772b73ccf9aac","text":"Launch permissions","correct":true}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWS’s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"520b9022-2fa7-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your company needs the support of concierge-level account specialists to help with billing and account subjects. Which of the following AWS Support pricing plans provides that feature?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan will provide a Concierge Support Team, which is a group of account specialists to assist your company with their billing and accounting questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","title":"AWS Enterprise Support"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false}]},{"id":"h0bz8vyv-zk25-7xf6-p1l3-v0qntk7m5yjw","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are types of cloud computing deployments?","explanation":"The three types of cloud deployments are: \r\n Public - where everyone and anyone can access that cloud's resources \r\n Private - also called on-premises where the underlying cloud infrastructure is owned and operated by a private entity for the sole use of that entity \r\n Hybrid - which is a mix of both. \r\n Mixed cloud is not a term used to describe a cloud computing deployment","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"2dde6ce98c19e445f3c47a7a9d166f04","text":"Hybrid cloud","correct":true},{"id":"761883c0d5c55fba5b200ac8ac0d86e5","text":"Public cloud","correct":true},{"id":"cb38b39495aded16d3565297386a9c9e","text":"Private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"7d22e2d665f6d51244a33f26e96904f9","text":"Mixed cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true}]},{"id":"84676206-45b7-4b8d-b856-91c915e8d017","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS service usages is free for the first 12 months after signup for an AWS account?","explanation":"Upon signup for an AWS account, you get 750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month for the first 12 months.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"af41413a0bb72142c1ce2257ac3a184f","text":"1 million AWS Lambda requests per month","correct":false},{"id":"02cbe76727c54b36b3ff3915aa629fae","text":"25 GB of Amazon DynamoDB storage","correct":false},{"id":"159df35cfb0a136f46cbecfe096e2468","text":"750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month","correct":true},{"id":"267c5706cefc5dc9fb06ecdab987b079","text":"1 million API Gateway calls received per month","correct":false}]},{"id":"d18562b0-19ef-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"VPC, CloudFront, and Route 53 are examples of what type of AWS service?","explanation":"Amazon VPC, Amazon CloudFront, and Amazon Route 53 are networking and content delivery services that AWS offers. VPC and Route 53 are involved with linking resources with one another to operate interactively; VPC creates a virtual network, and Route 53 connects end users to web applications. CloudFront is an AWS service for fast web content delivery.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/networking-services.html","title":"Networking and Content Delivery"}],"answers":[{"id":"e9a86c354aaf76a2e678148d3d2b9817","text":"Migration and Transfer","correct":false},{"id":"57c28ff1fb9ea9b16bc846660a260623","text":"Networking and Content Delivery","correct":true},{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false}]},{"id":"p591e7kl-wfkp-78wh-zz8y-kf2mmf34gdw1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are steps you should take in securing your AWS account?","explanation":"The Root account should have MFA enabled, due to it's unlimited access to an account. You should always create IAM users for individual users, since the Root account should never be used for actual work. Groups should be used to delegate permissions to the users you create, instead of individual assigning policies to IAM users since it makes administration easier. Assigning policies directly to any user is not a good idea, since it can be hard to figure out who has access to what resources with many users.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM best practice"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_create_for-user.html","title":"IAM using Roles"}],"answers":[{"id":"bd3cf659e9d378f1808cdb33b54baa84","text":"Assign policies directly to your administrative users","correct":false},{"id":"2e679971f295b42ffb5f0228883437fb","text":"Use groups to delegate access to IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"8ef2b84b0ea8ddc5ae686a44387d63d7","text":"Activate Multi-factor Authentication (MFA) on your root account.","correct":true},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true}]},{"id":"83246738-477a-40c5-8224-59d739ad6600","domain":"tech","question":"You are a solutions architect working for a New York-based digital marketing company specializing in local SEO. You are tasked with creating an S3 bucket to operate within the US West (N. California) Region. The company wants to name it with the IP address of the SEO Health Checker application that was recently developed for potential clients based in California to get a free website analysis report. Which of these actions would be most appropriate?","explanation":"Bucket names must not be formatted as an IP address. Indeed, each bucket name should be unique across all existing names in Amazon S3. So, following AWS naming rules, name the bucket after the type of data it will store.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"557ad9f77b4777473a400e65c0bc146a","text":"Do not name the bucket after the application’s IP address.","correct":true},{"id":"dc1cf44cc05f915cfa69e23237b4e6c0","text":"Simply name the bucket after the Region.","correct":false},{"id":"73d20a8bf6fd3ae4e325f0aba2e8a8c6","text":"Use dashes instead of periods in the IP address to comply with bucket naming rules.","correct":false},{"id":"49336715d3a6034152315aaa72ba1ca2","text":"That shouldn’t be a problem; name the bucket after the web application’s IP address.","correct":false}]},{"id":"mgnw8w23-ecuc-6otr-478z-r3k8sv03qrcj","domain":"tech","question":"Your application needs fully-managed storage for objects. Which of the following options should you choose?","explanation":"S3 is fully-managed storage for objects. EBS provides virtual hard disks in the cloud and is block-based not object-based. EC2 is a compute service, and RDS is a database service.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true},{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false},{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true},{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"a1237c57-f005-8048-710c-489f984ca8d0","domain":"tech","question":"Where would you find the AWS Attestation of Compliance Documentation for PCI DSS?","explanation":"AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS’ security and compliance reports and select online agreements. AWS Support's site provides general information about compliance, but does not hold the secure reports or certificates. AWS IAM is used to control security within your AWS Account. Amazon Macie is a data security classification service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/","title":"AWS Artifact"}],"answers":[{"id":"1f7efb5a61d1162575c83917dd086ad7","text":"Amazon Macie","correct":false},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"73bf7f67bbb8ede06c6d98f4133f9743","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"60b018772cea138af5a8c452ed694734","text":"AWS Artifact","correct":true}]},{"id":"6sole68h-iivl-m9l8-zztc-bfdk38rdagvy","domain":"security","question":"In which order is a user granted access to AWS services?","explanation":"The user is Authenticated, then Authorized to use AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"0d3c25cb8fbf51013a4258262d14a6ff","text":"The user is Authorized, then Authenticated.","correct":false},{"id":"a6a56d56f380bafb99d9c83d0ea32240","text":"The user is Authenticated, then Authorized to use AWS services.","correct":true}]},{"id":"5l7vjhuv-wf9j-de1i-9aj4-e9dlg8u6cc76","domain":"billing","question":"Your Development team uses four on-demand EC2 instances, and your QA team has 5 reserved instances, only three of which are being used. Assuming all AWS accounts are under a single AWS Organization, how will the Development team's instances be billed?","explanation":"Assuming all instances are in the same AWS Organization, the reserved instance pricing for the unused QA instances will be applied to two of the four Dev instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecadbc09799c3807dfed5bd9ee9c6159","text":"All the Dev team's instances will be billed at the on-demand rate.","correct":false},{"id":"3ea9a50157f205cce00d0db169117711","text":"All the Dev instances will be billed at the reserved instance rate.","correct":false},{"id":"b04b07a9c68b5b505f53afccb5616743","text":"The pricing for the reserved instances will shift from QA to Dev.","correct":false},{"id":"a6d19cc18b59af08baaa0f8247fca355","text":"The Dev team will be billed for two instances at on-demand prices and two instances at the reserved instance price.","correct":true}]},{"id":"fde3bfdf-a9fa-4476-b785-b8de7b315aeb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following languages can be used to author CloudFormation templates?","explanation":"CloudFormation supports both JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) and YAML Ain't Markup Language (aka YAML) for authoring CloudFormation templates.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/working-with-templates-cfn-designer-json-editor.html","title":"Integrated JSON and YAML Editor"}],"answers":[{"id":"0ecd11c1d7a287401d148a23bbd7a2f8","text":"JSON","correct":true},{"id":"a7f5f35426b927411fc9231b56382173","text":"Python","correct":false},{"id":"9463f87bbed1fcdacfb8d40e185ca2bc","text":"YAML","correct":true},{"id":"2a52ba6e26e550c59e15affa051e478b","text":"CAMEL","correct":false}]},{"id":"2srflb2w-gpba-wyok-a3ts-v64r4v1vd57h","domain":"tech","question":"You use containers to host your microservices, and you need to route traffic to those applications using a single load balancer. Which of the following services should you use to accomplish this?","explanation":"This routing can be done only with an Application Load Balancer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/details/#details","title":"About the ALB"}],"answers":[{"id":"7be6a0f173a965818e92c1df46c6626e","text":"AWS CodeDeploy","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":true},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false}]},{"id":"hmh7tnlm-n4hf-9v8o-75e5-uksbwqwddinx","domain":"tech","question":"For which of the below is S3 a suitable storage solution?","explanation":"S3 is object storage suitable for the storage of 'flat' files like documents, photos, etc. Use cases which require very atomic or consistent reading and writing, such as databases and operating systems, are more suited to EBS (Elastic Block Store) storage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea2ef9b0d095bf991f4973633b485340","text":"Databases","correct":false},{"id":"b11ddc7e1671c0bd22dc89dd757508d4","text":"Pictures","correct":true},{"id":"f28128b38efbc6134dc40751ee21fd29","text":"Documents","correct":true},{"id":"aab338915e32b60e92c8de3a23aa5c5d","text":"Operating Systems","correct":false}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false},{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false},{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true}]},{"id":"82a1ac91-eb42-41c9-b216-39000de68a5c","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following statements are true about who can use IAM roles?","explanation":"A role can be used by either an IAM user in the same AWS account as the role or a user in a different AWS account. A role can also be used by a web service that AWS offers; a prime example is Amazon EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_terms-and-concepts.html","title":"IAM Role Terms and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"bf2d86ed19745c25bb11a0239b17b7a5","text":"An IAM user in a different AWS account than the role","correct":true},{"id":"31124384faad90d323f0ac8b670e3d5f","text":"An IAM user in the same AWS account as the role","correct":true},{"id":"85f661e32207f8f663f531db040bc97a","text":"A web service offered by AWS","correct":true},{"id":"df8acd03a312147855a4dbb0fc3cad51","text":"A web service offered by providers other than AWS","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false},{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false},{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false}]}]}}}}
